<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Thomas Davey-Spence</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Thomas Davey-Spence</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 18:27:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog: Forced To Provide Your PINs &amp; Tech: A Modern Day Nightmare Scenario</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/nightmare-scenario/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 18:27:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/nightmare-scenario/</guid><description>Today I was browsing as usual, when I came across a terrifying thread. Someone talking about being mugged in London, a scary enough experience, but with a twist. The individual was forced to hand over the pin for their numbers for cards, and the password to their phone. Giving the attackers access to pretty much anything on the phone that didn’t have extra layers of security.
I want you to think for a minute, what is on your phone?</description></item><item><title>Blog: How does ChatGPT fair against leetcode?</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/ai-research-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/ai-research-2/</guid><description>I chose a difficult question, but one that is relatively common, merging linked-lists. I used the “Merge k Sorted Lists” problem in GoLang.
/** * Definition for singly-linked list. * type ListNode struct { * Val int * Next *ListNode * } */ func mergeKLists(lists []*ListNode) *ListNode { if len(lists) == 0 { return nil } var mergeTwoLists func(*ListNode, *ListNode) *ListNode mergeTwoLists = func(l1 *ListNode, l2 *ListNode) *ListNode { if l1 == nil { return l2 } if l2 == nil { return l1 } if l1.</description></item><item><title>Blog: Fun with ChatGPT: Explanations</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/ai-research-1/images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/ai-research-1/images/</guid><description>I’m sure we’ve all been there before&amp;hellip; Sat in a webinar or meeting where people are discussing tech you&amp;rsquo;ve absolutely never heard of, you google it and still don&amp;rsquo;t understand what it does&amp;hellip;
But what if we could use a certain revolutionary new bit of tech to explain it to us in a way anyone, even a 5-year-old could understand? Well, that’s what I decided to have a go with.</description></item><item><title>Blog: My experience with the AZ-900: Tips &amp; Review</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/az-900-review/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/az-900-review/</guid><description>In January 2022 I pursued another certification at university, it should be noted that I did not pay for this certification, I instead received it as part of the Microsoft University Cloud Challenge so did not have to pay out of pocket for it.
I began studying for the AZ-900 in November 2021, making usage of the Microsoft Learn resources provided for free, I chose to re-use the methods I used for my Security+ for this certification.</description></item><item><title>Blog: A Review of Mimo's Web Development Course</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/mimo-web-dev-review/images/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 14:58:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/mimo-web-dev-review/images/</guid><description>Mimo Web Development Path Review
Mimo is a mobile app-based learning app, like Duolingo if you have ever given that a try. Based on short amounts of learning every day, over a long period of time. Earlier this year I took the plunge and spent £50 on Mimo premium to get access to the full web development and python courses (the only currently available). This week I finally completed the web development course, which at a pace of 1 5-minute lesson before work every day has taken me 6 months.</description></item><item><title>Blog: Building my first website with Hugo!</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/thesearchforawebsite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/thesearchforawebsite/</guid><description>After weeks of deliberation, I finally made the decision to start up a website. This will likely contain some little blogs and write-ups on various projects and milestones I work towards.
The issue with making a personal website is one I’m sure many in my position face: For a software engineer it is TOO EASY. With so many options available to build a fantastic looking, dynamic website; with hosting, certificates, domains all covered in one cost it almost feels like cheating.</description></item><item><title>Blog: Getting my Security+ without the reccomended experience</title><link>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/comptia-sec-writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thomas-davey-sec.com/posts/comptia-sec-writeup/</guid><description>After failing my driving test in November 2020 and unable to take more lessons due to the COVID lockdown I wanted something I could strive towards and attain in the time I found myself isolated. On a hunch I looked up the CompTIA Security+ a certification I regularly saw mentioned in online InfoSec spaces. To my surprise I found a video course from Total Seminars on sale on Udemy, and decided to take the plunge.</description></item></channel></rss>